A Guide to the Environmental Impact Statements of the Dept. of Environmental Quality, 1976-2004
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Environmental Impact Statements of the Dept. of Environmental Quality, 1976-2004
The Library of Virginia
45114
15 cu. ft.
Virginia. Dept. of Environmental Quality
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Dept. of Environmental Quality on 26 July 2010.
Historical Information
The Dept. of Environmental Quality was created by an act of the General Assembly (effective April 1, 1993) by consolidating the programs, functions, staff, facilities, assets, and obligations of the State Water Control Board, the Dept. of Air Pollution Control (State Air Pollution Control Board), the Dept. of Waste Management (Virginia Waste Management Board), and the Council on the Environment. The director of the department is appointed by the Governor.
It is the policy of the Dept. of Environmental Quality to protect the environment of Virginia in order to promote the health and well-being of the Commonwealth's citizens by assisting in the effective implementation of state policies aimed at conserving the Commonwealth's natural resources and protecting its atmosphere, land and waters from pollution; coordinating permit review and issuance of procedures to protect all aspects of the environment; establishing and implementing a pollution prevention program to reduce the impact of pollutants; establishing procedures for and undertaking long-range environmental program planning and policy analysis; conducting comprehensive evaluations of the Commonwealth's environmental protection programs; providing for public education programs; developing uniform administrative systems to ensure coherent environmental policies; coordinating with federal agencies on environmental issues, such as environmental impact statements; promoting environmental quality through public hearings, permitting, inspection, monitoring and enforcement to enhance, preserve and protect Virginia's natural, scenic and historic environment; and advising the Governor and the General Assembly on matters relating to environmental quality.
Scope and Content
The Office of Environmental Impact Review coordinates the Commonwealth's response to environmental documents for proposed state and federal projects. The environmental impact review staff distributes documents to appropriate state agencies, planning districts and localities for their review and comment. Upon consideration of all comments, the staff prepares a single state response.
State agencies are required by the Virginia Code sections 10.1-1188 to prepare and submit environmental impact reports for construction of facilities that will cost $100,000 or more. The coordinated response is sent for consideration to the Secretary of Administration, who represents the Governor, under Executive Order 88(01). The Secretary's approval, after consideration of DEQ's comments, is required before funds can be released for a project.
Other types of state reviews coordinated by the Office include permits for the operation or expansion of public airports or landing fields. In addition, exploration for and extraction of minerals on state-owned lands and application for drilling permits into the Tidewater area require environmental impact statements. The Office also coordinates with the State Corporation Commission to review environmental reports for proposed power plants. Highway projects are handled exclusively by the Dept. of Transportation.
The National Environmental Policy Act requires environmental impact statements or assessments for certain classes of federal projects. The Office participates in scoping, draft document review, and final document review for these projects and coordinates federal intergovernmental review for all federal projects/actions and locally sponsored project that are federally funded. Also all federal projects/actions that directly affect Virginia's coastal zone must be carried out in a manner that is consistent with Virginia's Coastal Resources Management Program and the Office may review these projects for consistency during the National Environmental Policy Act process.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Environmental Impact Statements, 1976-2004.
Contents List
- Series I. Environmental Impact Statements, 1976-2004., Extent: 15 boxes. (Box 1-15)
  - Miscellaneous Projects
    - National Park Service: Manassas Battlefield Park Power Line Relocation, EA 1994, 94-057F, 1994. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority: Summary of Proposed Projects, 78-80 PEIS (Box 1)
    - Virginia Power: Goshen-Low Moor Transmission Line, PUE 9500, SCC 1995, 95-092C, 1995. (Box 1)
    - State Corporation Commission: Clover to Carson 500 kV Transmission Line, PUE 920058, 1993. (Box 1)
    - State Corporation Commission: Staff Report on the Restructuring of the Electric Industry, Case No. PUE950089, 1995. (Box 1)
    - State Corporation Commission: Competitive Market Forces in Electric Industry, 95-122C, 1995. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority: PMT Transit Shed Demo, 1986. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority: Newport News Marine Terminals Warehouses (Box 1)
    - U.S. Army - Crewe Industrial Park Access Road Federal Review (Box 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority: Master Plan for Norfolk Intr. Terminals, PEIS '78, 1978. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority: Imported Car Facility, EIS 1983-1984, 1983-1984. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority: Sewells Point Docks '77 PEIS, 1977. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority: Portsmouth Marine Terminal Master Plan EIS '76, 1976. (Box 1)
    - Independent Power Producer Requirements (Box 1)
    - DCR - E & S Guidelines for Transmission Lines (Box 1)
    - State Corporation Commission Environmental Study (Box 1)
    - U.S. Air Force: Emergency Beddown of the 309th Fighter Squadron & the 726th Air Control Squadron, EA 1993, 93-044F, 1993. (Box 1)
    - State Corporation Commission: Virginia Electric & Power Company Certificate of Public Convenience & Necessity, PUE 2003-00395, DEQ 03-172S, 2003. (Box 1)
    - State Corporation Commission: Multitude of Pittsylvania County LP 80 MW Generating Facility in the Town of Hurt, PUE 2004-00089, 2004. (Box 1)
    - State Corporation Commission: Commonwealth Atlantic Ltd Partnership 312 MW, Facility in Chesapeake, VA, PUE 2004-00090, 2004. (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous State Corporation Commission Projects
    - Patowmack Power Partners: Patowmack Power Generation Facility, SCC 1955, 95-090C, 1995. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission Transmission Line Application Guidelines - Minimum Requirements (May 10, 1991); Information Required for Approval of New Generation Facilities, 1986. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission/Virginia Natural Gas Inc.: Measurement and Regulation Station, 95-029C, 1995. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: East Danville-Roxboro 230 kV Transmission Line, 96-142C, 1996. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission/Virginia Gas Pipeline Co.: P-25 Gas Pipeline from Chilhowie to Radford Draft Assessment, 97-045C, 1997. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission CLM Task Force (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: Conservation & Load Management Policy Initiative, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Virginia Power - Demand Management Plan (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: Virginia Gas Pipeline Application for Certificate of Public Convenience & Necessity, SCC, 96-179C, 1996. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: Transmission Line Guidelines, 94-053C, 1994. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: Mecklenburg Electric Cooperative Proposal in Halifax County (DCC 94061012), EA 1994, 94-058C, 1994. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: Virginia Power - City of Alexandria Transmission Line Underground Installation Phase II, 96-087C, 1996. (Box 2)
    - Eagles - Powell Creek (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: 1-13th & Bank Parking 2-14th & Grace Parking, 3-Office/Parking, PEIS, 1987. (Box 2)
    - Evaluation of Utility Company 10 and 20 Year Plans (Required by SCC/Va. Code), 1997. (Box 2)
    - APCO: Smith Mountain Turbine Replacement and Upgrade, SCC 2996, 96-066C, 1996. (Box 2)
    - REC - Rappahannock County (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: Virginia Power - City of Alexandria Transmission Line Underground Installation, 96-028C, 1996. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: Rappahannock Electrical Co-Op: Profitt - Rivanna Line & Substation, App. 1992, 92-043S, 1992. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission: APCO Projects - Danville (Box 2)
  - Environmental Impact Review Chronological Files
    - 1989. (Box 3)
    - 1994. (Box 3)
    - 1990. (Box 3)
    - 1991 Aug.-Dec. (Box 3)
    - 1991 Jan.-July (Box 3)
    - 1991 Aug.-Dec. (Box 3)
    - 1992. (Box 3)
    - 1993. (Box 3)
    - 1992 Jan. (Box 4)
    - 1992 Feb. (Box 4)
    - 1992 March. (Box 4)
    - 1992 April. (Box 4)
    - 1992 May. (Box 4)
    - 1992 June. (Box 4)
    - 1992 July. (Box 4)
    - 1992 Aug. (Box 4)
    - 1992 Sept. (Box 4)
    - 1992 Oct. (Box 4)
    - 1992 Nov. (Box 4)
    - 1992 Dec. (Box 4)
    - 1993 Jan. (Box 5)
    - 1993 Feb. (Box 5)
    - 1993 March. (Box 5)
    - 1993 April. (Box 5)
    - 1993 May. (Box 5)
    - 1993 June. (Box 5)
    - 1993 July. (Box 5)
    - 1993 Aug.. (Box 5)
    - 1993 Sept. (Box 5)
    - 1993 Oct. (Box 5)
    - 1993 Nov. (Box 5)
    - 1993 Dec. (Box 5)
    - 1994 Jan. (Box 6)
    - 1994 Feb. (Box 6)
    - 1994 March. (Box 6)
    - 1994 April. (Box 6)
    - 1994 May. (Box 6)
    - 1994 June. (Box 6)
    - 1994 July. (Box 6)
    - 1994 Aug. (Box 6)
    - 1994 Sept. (Box 6)
    - 1994 Oct. (Box 6)
    - 1994 Nov. (Box 6)
    - 1994 Dec. (Box 6)
  - Lake Gaston
    - Lake Gaston Newspaper Articles, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston Newspaper Articles, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston Newspaper Articles, 1983-1985 (Box 7)
    - C of E: Lake Gaston Newspaper Project, Draft EA, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston Newspaper Articles, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston Newspaper Duplicate Material (Box 7)
    - ACOE: Virginia Beach Water Supply, Lake Gaston Pipeline, EA 1983, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston Water Supply VMRC 83-0747, Appeal of NC Objection, NC Objection, 1991 (Box 7)
    - DOE: Corps: Lake Gaston Permit Modification, 1992 (Box 7)
    - FERC: Vepco Easement Application for Virginia Beach Gaston Project, 91-009F, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston: MRC Permit Revision, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - Gaston Pipeline, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston: Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 95-013F, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston - Comments on Boyle Eng. Report, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston: Scooping (Box 7)
    - Corps: Lake Gaston Supp. EA, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston: Summary Document, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Lake Gaston: Legal Aspects (Box 7)
  - Lake Gaston & Miscellaneous Projects
    - Lake Gaston - Wilder's Letter, KJB Comments to Commerce re. Gaston, 1991-1993 (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Informal Notes (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Final EA: Documents (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Final EA: Information (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Citizen Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Extra Papers (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Public Hearings (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: News Articles (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Information (Box 8)
    - Dept. of Commerce Lake Gaston Hearing, 1992 (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Hoffman News Conference, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston Water Supply Project - Virginia Beach (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Congressional Hearing (Box 8)
    - Lake Gaston: Final EA: Correspondence and Response (Box 8)
    - State Corporation Commission/APCO: Transmission Line - Smith Mountain to Penhook Station, 1994 (Box 8)
    - State Corporation Commission: Authorization to Construct a Generating Facility in Accomack County (Commonwealth Ches. Corp) 96-191C (Box 8)
    - Central Virginia Electrical Coop: Transmission Line Improvements, 94-051C, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Elko Tract
    - DMA - Virginia Public Safety Complex on Elko Tract - BEIS, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract - COE Meeting, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract - Natural Area Preserve, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract - Miscellaneous Documents (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract - Sewer Line Inquiry, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract (DMA, DEB) (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract - Forestry Timber Harvest, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract - Overall Information (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract Public Safety Complex: Driver Training Track, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
    - Elko Tract - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 9)
    - Proposed Master Plan (Box 9)
    - Land Use Plan (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous Projects
    - Power Line Review: APCO, Wyoming - Cloverdale, 1991 (Box 10)
    - State Corporatrion Commission: Development of Standards for Resource Planning, Conservation, & Efficiency for Power Generation, 95-033C, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Common to APCO & VEPCO (Box 10)
    - Federal Review: APCO-Wyoming - Cloverdale Transmission Line, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Federal Projects (Box 10)
    - Ft. Eustis (Box 10)
    - SEI/Birchwood, 1991 (Box 10)
    - State Projects (Box 10)
    - Power Line Review: Virginia Power, N. Pole J Jump, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Chesterfield County: Proposed Coalbed Wells, EIA 1995, 95-059, 1995 (Box 10)
    - BG Clips Info on Power Lines (Box 10)
    - Electrical Transmission Lines/Health Effects (Box 10)
    - FERC: Roanoke River Basin, 1991 (Box 10)
    - State Corporation Commission: Restructuring and Competition, Independent Systems Operators, PUE 950089 and PUE 980138 (Box 10)
    - A Phase I Architectural Survey of the Proposed Clover to Carson 500 kV Transmission Line, Halifax, Charlotte, Mecklenburg, Brunswick, & Dinwiddie Counties, Management Summary, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Application of Virginia Electric & Power Company for Approval of Electric Facilities, Clover to Carson 500 kV Transmission Line, Application No. 197, Case No. PUE9200, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Direct Testimony and Exhibits of Virginia Electric & Power Company, Before the State Corporation, Clover to Carson 500 kV Transmission Line, Application No. 197, Case No. PUE920058, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Environmental Assessment for the Clover to Carson 500 kV Transmission Line Project for Virginia Power, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: ACFCMA Regulations for a Closed Area to Fishing for Horseshoe Crabs in the Exclusive Economic Zone, EA/FCD 2000, 00-096F, 2000 (Box 11)
    - NMS: Adjustment 7 Sea Scallop Fishery Management Plan, 96-016A, 1996 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/NMS: Amend Regulations Governing Swordfish, Federal Consistency, 96-049A, 1996 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Amendment to the Large Whale Take Reduction Plan (ALWTRP), EA 2000, 00-137F, 2000 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: FEIS - Amendment 8 to FMP for the Summer Flounder, Adding the Scup Fishery, FC 1996, 96-098A, 1996 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Amendment 12 to FMP/Coastal Migratory Pelagic Resources (Mackerels) Gulf of Mexico/S. Atlantic, FCD 1999, 99-127F, 1996 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Annual Adjustment to Summer Flounder FMP, Federal Consistency, 96-101A, 1996 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Atlantic Blue/White Marlin, Billfish, Federal Consistency, 1998 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Atlantic Bluefin Tuna Annual Specifications & Regulatory Amendment, FCD 2000, 00-065F, 2000 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Atlantic Bluefin Tuna Quotas, 1997 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Atlantic Blue/White Marlin, Billfish, Federal Consistency, 96-068A, 1996 (Box 11)
    - Atlantic Sea Scallop Fishery Management Plan - Amendment 7, Federal Consistency, 1998 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Atlantic Shark Fisheries, Federal Consistency, 1997 (Box 11)
    - NMF/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Atlantic Swordfish & shark Fisheries, Federal Consistency, 96-136A, 1996 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Ban on Sale of Undersize Swordfish - Federal Consistency, 1998 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Black Sea Bass FMP, Federal Consistency, 96-117A, 1996 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Chesapeake Bay National Estuarine Research Res. System in Virginia, FEIS 1990, 1990 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Coastal NonPoint Pollution Control Program, State of Virginia, EA 1997, 97-107F, 1996 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Coastal NonPoint Pollution Control Program, EIS 1996, 96-039F, 1996 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/OCRM: Coastal Zone Management Act Federal Consistency Regulations Proposed Rule, FC 2000, 00--52F, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/NOS: DCZMA Consistency Compliance Requirements, ACOE's O & M Projects, 1997 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Draft Amendment 8 to the Fisheries Management Plan for Coastal Migratory Pelagic Resources, EIS 1996, 96-008F, 1996 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Draft Amendment 1 to the Atlantic Billfish Fishery FMP, Federal Consistency Review, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Effects of Electromagnetic Radiation from Weather Radar, Supp EA 1992, 92-022F, 1992 (Box 11)
    - NEFMC: Essential Fish Habitat Amendment to FMPs, Federal Consistency Review, 1998 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Essential Fish Habitat, Proposed Rule, 1997 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/NMFA: Federal Action to Prohibit Use of Driftnets in the Directed Atlantic Swordfish Fishery, 1998 (Box 11)
    - MAFMC: FMP Atlantic Surfclam & Ocean Quahog Fisheries, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Department of Commerce/National Marine Fisheries Service/NEFMC: Framework Adjustment 14 to the Atlantic Sea Scallop Fishery Management Plan, DSEIS 2000, 00-156B, 2000 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/SAFMC: Framework Seasonal Adjustment/Harvest Levels & Related Measures Fishery Plan/Mackerels, FCD 2000, 00-027F, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Department of Commerce/National Marine Fisheries Service: Interim Rule Concerning Atlantic Sea Scallop Fishery Management Plan, Federal Consistency, 1998 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce: Interim Rule to Implement 2000 Spiny Dogfish Specifications, FCD 2000, 00-047F, 1997 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/NMFA: Interstate Mangement Plan for Weakfish, 1997 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: National Marine Fisheries Service - Fisheries Management Plans, 1993 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/NMFA: 1999 Summer Flounder, Scup, & Black Sea Bass Specifications - Federal Consistency, 1998 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: North Atlantic Right Whale Protection, 1997 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Nonpoint Pollution Control Program Guidance - Final Administration Changes, 98-092F, 1998 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Proposed Bluefin Tuna Quotas & Procedural Changes, 96-065A, 1996 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/NMFA: Proposed Federal Action for the Atlantic Bluefin Tuna Fisheries, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Department of Commerce/National Marine Fisheries Service: Proposed Regime to Govern Interactions Between Marine Mammals & Commercial Fishing Operations, 91-044F, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/NMFA: Proposed Rules for Specifications & Effort Controls/Atlantic Bluefin Tuna Quotas, 1998 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Removal of Federal Ban to Harvest & Possess Atlantic Striped Bass, Propsed regulatory Action, 95-129A, 1995 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Swordfish Management Pilot Program, 92-078F, 1992 (Box 11)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/MAFMC: Tilefish Fishery Managment Plan, 099-086F, 1999 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/NMFA: Time/Area Closures for Pelagic Longlin Fishing, 99-133F, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: DSEIS of Federal Lobster Management in the Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ) DSEIS 2000, 00-142F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Bluefish Specifications for the Year 2001, 00-142F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - New England Fishery Management Council: Amendment 7 to Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan, 1996 (Box 12)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration: Summer Flounder Scup and Black sea Bass Specifications, 00-010F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Taking if Marine Mammals for Shock Trial of Winston S. Churchill, Navy, 00-035F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: 2001 Atlantic Mackerel, Squid, & Butterfish Initial Specifications, 00-120F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Rulemaking to Allow Dual Permit Status Fishing Vessels Exemption from Lobster Trap Gear Restrictions, 00-099F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Regulatory Amendment for Highly Migratory Species Dealer Reporting & Fishing Allocations, 00-157F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Modification to the Scup Gear Restricted Areas, Atlantic Mackerel & Small-Mesh Fisheries, 00-121F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Virginia's Non-Compliance with Atlantic State MFC's IFMP for Horseshoe Crab, 00-095F, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Amendment 9 to the Summer Flounder Fishery Management Plan: Fishery Management Plan & Final Environmental Impact Statement for the Black Sea Bass Fishery, 1996 (Box 12)
    - Final Amendment 5 to the Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan Incorporating the Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement, Volume I, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Final Amendment 5 to the Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan Incorporating the Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement, Volume II, 1993 (Box 12)